[{"answer": "city halls", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 6, "question": "", "qSentId": 5},{"answer": " Really cold out here tonight isnt it", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 15, "question": "city halls", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Yes. I need my coat. Could I bum a cigarette", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Really cold out here tonight isnt it", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Sure, here I think its supposed to snow later tonight", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Yes. I need my coat. Could I bum a cigarette", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " (Cough) I wish we could smoke inside", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Sure, here I think its supposed to snow later tonight", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Yeah, what happened to the smoking area? I dont see the sign anymore", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 19, "question": " (Cough) I wish we could smoke inside", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " The new city law states you cant smoke inside anymore", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Yeah, what happened to the smoking area? I dont see the sign anymore", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " I was surprised when I was told to step outside after I lit my cigarette.  I eat her", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 21, "question": " The new city law states you cant smoke inside anymore", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " I read it in the newspaper a few days ago", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 25, "question": " I was surprised when I was told to step outside after I lit my cigarette.  I eat her", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " I didnt realize it was going to be so soon", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 29, "question": " I read it in the newspaper a few days ago", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Yes, apparently a lot of places now have instituted laws just like this so now", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 30, "question": " I didnt realize it was going to be so soon", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Why is that", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Yes, apparently a lot of places now have instituted laws just like this so now", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Scientists have studied that people in a room with you who are not smoking", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Why is that", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Fewer people are smoking now", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Scientists have studied that people in a room with you who are not smoking", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " They are trying to let young people know how bad smoking is before they start", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Fewer people are smoking now", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": "Well, I suppose that is a good thing. I started smoking when I was 15 years old", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 42, "question": " They are trying to let young people know how bad smoking is before they start", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": "I started when I was 17. I quit when I got pregnant but went right back to it afte", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Well, I suppose that is a good thing. I started smoking when I was 15 years old", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Yeah, I have tried to quit myself", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 47, "question": "I started when I was 17. I quit when I got pregnant but went right back to it afte", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " I know my son has been nagging me to quit after he learned about it in school", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Yeah, I have tried to quit myself", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " There are some things at the pharmacy that can help you quit", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 49, "question": " I know my son has been nagging me to quit after he learned about it in school", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Yeah, there are, and its getting really expensive to buy cigarettes. I pai", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 50, "question": " There are some things at the pharmacy that can help you quit", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Yes, its becoming very expensive to smoke.  Most of my friends who used t", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Yeah, there are, and its getting really expensive to buy cigarettes. I pai", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Yesthat may be the only way. I mean sticking these cancer sticks in ou", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Yes, its becoming very expensive to smoke.  Most of my friends who used t", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Yeah, look at usout here in the cold, our friends are inside, there is good foo", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Yesthat may be the only way. I mean sticking these cancer sticks in ou", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": "It does seem kind of sillywell, it was nice talking with you", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Yeah, look at usout here in the cold, our friends are inside, there is good foo", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Im glad we had this conversation.  Im going to think again next time I buy a pac", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 67, "question": "It does seem kind of sillywell, it was nice talking with you", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Yes, and good luck to you", "docId": "11-08", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Im glad we had this conversation.  Im going to think again next time I buy a pac", "qSentId": 70}]
